she is from legal and she is potentially
她来自法律界，而且很有可能是
a very expensive sexual harassment
非常昂贵的性骚扰
lawsuit oddly more like that yes and
诉讼更奇怪的是，是的
I've got three excellent potential
我有三个极好的潜力
candidates better lined up and ready
候选人最好排好队，做好准备
meet you I don't have time to meet I
我没有时间和你见面
need someone now I feel like it's her no
现在我需要一个人，我觉得是她不
it's not we have a box before I have yes
在我有盒子之前我们没有是的
I like tae bo booty boot camp crunchy
我喜欢棒棒糖
something like that how do I spell your
我怎么拼写你的
name Natalie are you what are you gonna
娜塔莉，你你要怎么做
google her hmm
谷歌她嗯
I thought I was going her oh wow very
我以为我要去她那里
very impressive individual she's French
她是法国人，令人印象深刻
Italian Russian Latin who speaks Latin
讲拉丁语的意大利俄裔拉丁人
no one speaks Latin there was dead
没有人会说拉丁语
language you can read Latin or you can
语言你可以读拉丁文也可以
write Latin but I'm yeah Kashima
写拉丁文，但我是卡什玛
[Music]
(音乐)